3RD FLOOR GIANT LABYRINTH
BANQUET
HAUNTED HOUSE
TAKOYAKI
EIMEI FESTIVAL
[boy 1] Don't hit anything.
[boy 2] To the right. The right.
[boy 3] Let's lift it.
[boys] One, two, three...
SNOW WHITE SCRIPT
[all exclaiming]
Looks like it's ready.
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
You can't tell me that
the day before the festival!
Oh, come on, Inomata.
EPISODE 19
I'VE GOT PLANS
This just means that your play is gonna
have to start about ten minutes earlier.
A little mistake slipped through
on the pamphlet, so...
Year one, Class B, 3:30 start.
There we go.
[grunts angrily]
[Taiki] I'll be on my way.
TEACHERS' LOUNGE
I can't believe
he didn't check it more carefully.
That's ten whole minutes!
[pleasant music playing]
The hustle and bustle really makes it feel
like the day before the school festival.
[gasps]
You're askin' Kano?
To go around the festival with you?
There's no way that's happening!
Like I've got a shot with her.
I guess she looks pretty busy, too.
[boy 2] Exactly!
[boy 1] Gazing from afar is enough for me.
- [Taiki sighs]
- [boy 2] I wish I could join that circle.
[boy 1] Give it up.
Hey, Taiki!
Have you mentally prepared to go in there?
- Prepared?
- You're in for a surprise when you do!
[Taiki] Don't tell me someone
broke a set piece again.
[Takada] No, that's not it.
- [girls exclaiming]
- You look so freakin' cute!
[girl 2] You look so beautiful.
[overlapping chatter]
[pleasant music playing]
[exclaims softly]
[gasps]
[girl 3] It's totally perfect!
You really came through
with this one, Kyo.
Mm-hm.
At least it got finished in time.
Oh, and our fearless leader,
tell her what you think.
[gasps] Oh...
Um, I...
Yeah, it looks okay, I guess.
[Niina scoffs] That all you've got?
Hey! I need your help with my hair.
[Niina] It seemed like he was
just about to say something nice!
- You don't have to run.
- [Hina] Uh--
[Niina] I guess she felt awkward
around him, too.
- So about the play's...
- [Niina] And it's not as if
- Hina isn't on Inomata's mind either.
- Now it's gotta be ten minutes earlier.
Here it is.
ONE MORE DAY!
[Niina] Is it possible something might
happen during the festival?
CREPES
TAKOYAKI
LABYRINTH - 2-B CAFE
HISTORICAL PLAY
[Yukiko] What? You're kidding me, right?
Today's the festival, isn't it?
Why are you in workout clothes?
[Taiki] I can't go to the gym
'cause of the festival.
So I'm going for a run.
I'll see you a little later!
[door opens, closes]
[sighs] That boy
could take a day off for once.
[footsteps running]
[panting]
HIT THAT SMASH!
- Chinatsu!
- Uh.
Taiki.
What are you doing here?
Morning practice
because the gym is closed.
You know you could
take a day off for once.
That goes for you, too.
It's like, I have so much motivation
after the match the other day.
I feel the same way.
Seeing you play like that got me fired up.
[gasps]
Although, at this rate,
I'll never be able to catch up with you.
Could you please take some more pit stops
on your way to greatness?
Well, sure. I'm taking pit stops.
That's a lie.
Your brain is 100% basketball. [grunts]
That's not true.
[Taiki] She's so cool.
She truly lives for the sport.
You know what?
So the band we heard the other day
is made up of second years.
Really?
I heard their concert is at two o'clock.
Let's go see them together.
[gasps softly]
If you're not free, that's okay.
No, I'm in!
That's awesome!
[alarm ringing]
ALARM
SNOOZE
Oh, I've gotta get going.
All right, so two o' clock. See you there.
Got it.
Got it...
[grunts]
[groans]
CONGRATULATIONS ON NATIONALS
[female announcer] The Eimei School
Cultural Festival is now open.
EIMEI FESTIVAL
Here we go!
Taste my deadly Butterfly Rings! Ha!
- [ring toss guy] Oh, what a bummer!
- [whimpers]
- I'm going again!
- [ring toss guy whimpers]
- She's having fun.
- [Hina squeals]
- I wonder if she's ever nervous.
- [Hina] One more time!
Isn't she only that upbeat
because she's probably feeling nervous?
And the play's starting at 3:30, right?
If she has to start getting ready by 3:00,
she's gotta pack it all in before then.
Good point.
It's time for me
to start making my rounds now.
What are you getting up to?
For now, I'll go find Sho and the others,
and after that...
All right, so two o'clock. See you there.
Oh, you know.
Something to do with Chinatsu?
- See you.
- Later.
[Taiki] It's like a dream come true.
Chinatsu invited me to a concert!
Huh?
Wait, Kishi?
Taiki Inomata!
I've heard the stories!
They say that you beat Yusa!
That's your opener?
You should take me on, too!
But we're at a festival.
Okay.
Then you gotta show me
where Chinatsu's class is.
I don't wanna!
What did you just say?
You're the one who's standing in my way
of getting her phone number, remember?
Yeah, and it was only because you lost!
[both grunting]
Well!
There's a combo you don't see often.
Hi, Haryu. And hello, Karen.
CULTURAL FESTIVAL ATTIRE
MODEL GIRLFRIEND
TWO GUYS
SAD FIGHT
[both grunt]
Why are you guys having this big fight?
Well, Miss Karen,
this doofus won't escort me
to where Year 2 Class B is.
"Miss Karen"?
Well, we were just on our way there,
so why don't you tag along?
If you don't mind!
Although,
it's quite stimulating, so be careful.
[both] Huh?
CAFÉ
[indistinct chatter]
[sparkling sound]
Hi! Welcome in!
[girl] Waitress!
I'll be right with you.
[both exclaiming]
[girl] Chinatsu!
Yes?
Sorry for making you wait.
[groans]
Kishi!
[gasping] How are you
still on your feet, bro?
It's not easy.
I'm fighting for my life here.
[both] She's just too cute.
Those two are funny ones.
They're young.
[Taiki] That was a surprise.
She did tell me
she wasn't going to be a waitress.
I am glad I get to see her in that outfit,
but this is just...
Hello there.
You got a boyfriend?
Let me have your number.
Huh?
[exclaims]
We are not that kind of establishment.
Nagisa!
[Nagisa] So do me a favor,
and stop hitting on her.
She and I happen to operate
on the same wavelength.
We're a great combo.
Like PB&J.
Like a married couple who has
their own language to communicate.
Nagisa...
[Taiki] Thank goodness
there's someone protecting her.
[groans]
[Taiki] What?
Her... boyfriend?
Oh, no, that's one of her teammates from--
No better cure for heartbreak
than some drinking.
Go on, drink up.
You're using him for profit?
[sniffles]
I knew it'd turn out this way!
- [sniffles]
- [Taiki] How's he drunk?
[Kishi cries]
We may have had a magical meet-cute,
but it's not our destiny to be a couple.
A magical what?
[Kishi] Look at that smile on her face.
I'm okay,
as long as Chinatsu lives
happily ever after, I'll be all right.
[Haryu] That's it, drown your sorrows.
[Taiki] I want her to look happy
when it's me standing next to her.
- [footsteps approaching]
- [gasps]
[Karen] Chii, you're doing a great job.
[Chinatsu] You made it to the cafe!
[Karen] I thought that outfit
might need some divine worship.
What does that mean?
Pardon. I'll get a refill.
[Karen] So listen,
I wanna go to the fashion show.
And that starts at 2:00.
Chii! Let's go together.
[Taiki] What... Two o'clock is when...
Sorry, I have plans already.
- Okay, then what about you?
- [Taiki] Ah! Would you look at the time!
I have to go find my friends! Okay, bye!
- What the--
- Don't leave me!
[feel-good music playing]
[Taiki] The Cultural Festival is so fun.
MUSIC CLUB
2:00 P.M.
SAMOYED
SCHEDULE
[sighs]
Chinatsu sure is running late.
[grunts]
When she said, "See you there,"
did she mean "inside?"
Hey there. We are Samoyed.
[all cheering]
[Taiki] Incredible.
This is exciting.
[vocalist] Are you ready
to have a good time?
[all cheering]
[Taiki] There are
a lot of people here, but...
Wait. Maybe I misunderstood something?
SEE YOU AT TWO O'CLOCK
No, she definitely said that.
- Here's our first song.
- [Taiki] Then again...
- "Nagisa."
- [all cheering]
[Taiki] If you told me
it was all just a dream,
I wouldn't be surprised.
[boy] Yeah, let's go!
[Chinatsu panting]
I'm sorry...
I made you wait.
Sorry that I'm late.
[gasps softly]
It's that...
The person with the shift
after mine was late.
It's okay.
[vocalist] All right.
Here's our next song.
- [all cheering]
- Let's get closer.
[music playing]
[audience cheering]
[Taiki] What a relief.
It wasn't a dream after all.
[band singing "Nagisa" by Spitz]
This is my first concert,
but they're pretty awesome!
I guess it's too loud for her to hear me.
I said this is pretty awesome!
[chuckles] Mm-hm.
[Taiki] Why do I feel
like we're getting closer?
I wonder if I'm overthinking all of this.
I keep getting my hopes up over and over.
[all cheering]
Thank you, everyone!
And our next song is "Blues Drive."
- [all cheering]
- Oh! It's this song!
Do you like this one?
Yeah, I do, but actually,
Karen loves this song more.
She says she listens to it whenever
she and Haryu have a fight.
[music starts playing]
[band singing "Blues Drive"
by Yoshitaka Yamada]
Um, Chinatsu.
Why did you invite me
to come with you to the concert?
[grunts softly]
[Taiki] Ah. She couldn't hear me.
Just ignore what I said.
She probably just had
no one else to come with
because Karen was saying
she wanted to see the fashion show.
[exclaims softly]
[Chinatsu] It's because...
Did you say some...
[gasps]
Hang on, what did you just say?
Uh--
The music is too loud. Sorry!
What was it? Now I really wanna know.
That was fun, huh?
There's just nothing
like hearing music live.
Hey, about what you said before...
Your class's play starts soon.
It's at 3:30, right?
Yeah.
So she's just gonna pretend
she didn't hear me.
I'll get a seat right in the center.
You do know I'm not in it.
Even so,
I know you put a lot of work
into making it all happen.
FLUFFY AND CHEWY CREPES
Well, thanks for going with me.
- See ya.
- Okay.
[groans]
[Taiki] The Cultural Festival is so fun!
Only fun things happen when you're here!
We went to a concert together,
just the two of us!
If my life ever flashes before my eyes,
this'll be a day I remember.
Taiki! Hi.
STAMP RALLY
- Keep up the good work, Nishida.
- What? Hang on!
I'm super bored!
FORTUNE TELLER
[Taiki] All right.
What are you doing here?
I'm a fortune teller.
As you can see, my dear sir.
And beyond that,
my class is running a stamp rally,
and I'm one of the stamps you can get.
Inside, you'll find monsters and clowns,
and if you get stamps from them,
then, you can win a prize.
So are you in?
No, thanks.
DESTINY
Let me at least read your fortune.
Can you really do that?
Duh. My grandma's a psychic.
What?
[Nishida grunts]
How ominous!
Soon and very soon, a terrible
and unthinkable ordeal shall betide you!
Ordeal?
[girl] Mr. Fortune Teller!
I followed the advice you gave me,
and I found my wallet!
My ex-boyfriend texted me!
I found my long-lost brother!
You're an amazing fortune teller!
- [Nishida] I see. I see.
- Thank you so much!
[Taiki groans softly]
[Taiki] No, no, no.
There's no way what he said will happen.
An "unthinkable ordeal"
is too vague anyway.
WAITING ROOM
He probably just said
what came to his mind, and--
- [Niina] What?
- [Taiki grunts]
The actor playing the prince
is in the hospital?
She went to the Ninja Warrior booth.
She fell off after reaching the goal,
and she broke her leg.
[girl 1] Who's going
to play the prince, then?
[girl 2] We need someone to fill in.
Luckily, the prince
doesn't have too many lines.
- Anyone free?
- [boy 2] No, everyone's out having fun.
And everyone here
is an actor or needed backstage.
And I have to help with the lighting...
Hm. Oh.
[grunts softly]
Huh?
EIMEI FESTIVAL
[Niina] Oh!
[Taiki] Huh?!
[closing theme song playing]